

Stephen Barton

I am an experience and brand designer currently based in Portland, Oregon. My focus is on utilizing all touch points of a brand to create unique and authentic experiences, therefore encouraging the formation of communities. I am at my best when taking on projects that push me both creatively and analytically, allowing me to expand my skills and resources.

Knowledge Software: Skills:

Adobe Photoshop Brand Development/Strategy

Adobe Illustrator Brand Identity Design
Adobe InDesign Web/Digital Design
Adobe XD Experience Design
Wordpress UX Research
Squarespace UI Design

Tableau Front-End Development

Sketch Basic Python

Education 2014 – 2018

University of Colorado Boulder — Boulder, Colorado

B.S. in Strategic Communication focused on Advertising, PR, and Design Minor in Technology, Arts and Media

Experience

2018 - present

Self Employed

Freelance Experience and Brand Designer

Helping small businesses in the local community build their brands and connect with their customers. Working on aesthetics and strategy across all media, promoting brand consistency. Focusing on online presence and experience design.

2017 - 2018

The Rothwell Group L.P.

UX/UI and Marketing Intern

Focused on updating and creating modules within their HR software, BizRun, to improve usability. Kept the marketing website up to date and created iconography for the application.

2017 - 2018

University of Colorado Boulder

Research Assistant

Worked towards a better understanding of how people talk about time in reference to data and meta-data. Proposed ways to better communicate and manage time when working with others.